thewallpapers.org 2013-08-16

# Wallpapers | Desktop Wallpapers

## TheWallpapers User Policy

As TheWallpapers is a general-age website, we ask that all users behave in an appropriate manner at all times. As stated in the above Submissions Policy, we do not allow the use of offensive material. Do not post material that is pornographic, racial or hate-based. TheWallpapers reserves the right to cancel a member's access along with all files submitted by that member at any given time without warning. TheWallpapers also allows its users to remove their submissions at any given time.

### TheWallpapers Privacy Policy

**Information is collected at several points from users of the this site. TheWallpapers is the sole owner of this information and will not sell or disclose it to any third party. Information is gathered in the following situations:**

#### Cookies

TheWallpapers uses cookies to help make each user's visit easier and more interactive. By storing a cookie, the user does not have to log in to the site each time he/she visits the site and the user also gets to use features such as the messageboard and online chat. Cookies are in no way linked to the personal information disclosed at signup.

#### Outside Advertising

TheWallpapers uses outside advertising on its website. These advertising companies may also place cookies on your hard drive to collect information (not including name, email address and phone number) in regards to your visit to this and other sites in order to try and bring you advertising in relation to your interests.

#### IP Logging

TheWallpapers also logs IP addresses to help administer the website and track user's actions on the website. These details do not contain any personally identifiable information.

#### Sharing of Information

TheWallpapers will only share information with third parties if required to do so by law, or if by doing so we can protect the TheWallpapers website and/or it's users. If you do not wish for others to know your personal details (for example - name and email address), it is recommended that you do not apply for membership.

#### Links

TheWallpapers links to several other websites and does not control the content of any outside websites and can not be held accountable for their content. We also are not in control of the privacy policies of these sites and recommend that all members carefully read the privacy policies of other websites that collect personally identifiable information.

#### Children under the Age of 13

As TheWallpapers is a general-audience website, we can not allow children under the age of 13 to sign up for membership (in accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act). We ask that parents instead sign up for membership and monitor their children's activity on the website.

#### Changes to the Privacy Policy

If we make changes to this policy, we will let members know by posting mention of the changes on the homepage of this website. If we decide to use the personal details collected at membership signup (or during any other stage of a user's onsite activity) in any manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will let the user know via email. Users will be given a choice as to whether they want their information used in a different manner.

#### Contact TheWallpapers

If you have questions not answered in this policy in regards to the daily running of this site, please feel free to email at _info@TheWallpapers.org_

#### Advertising

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [networkadvertising.org](http://networkadvertising.org/).
